Taha Aamir

Johar Town | Lahore, Pakistan | 0314-4462746 | tahaaamir60@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/taha-aamir

Professional Summary

Marketing graduate with skills in digital marketing, social media and brand management. Experienced in creating effective campaigns and using analytics to drive results. Team player with a creative approach and strong problem – solving abilities. Ready to contribute to a dynamic marketing team.

Work Experience

Business Development Associate | Zameen.com | Lahore, Pakistan | 07/2024 – 08/2024

- Generating leads through outreach calls
- Building strong relationship with clients and property dealers
- Collaborate on sales strategy
- Analyze market trends to drive growth

Digital Marketer | AS Community HUB | Remote, Pakistan | 03/2024 – 08/2024

- Making strategic plans for clients to have effective results on their Facebook campaign
- Managing and optimizing social media pages on different platforms
- Effectively running the Facebook ads campaigns that derive results

Marketing Intern | Indus Home Appliances | Gujranwala | 06/2023 – 08/2023

- Generate potential leads for export
- Complete visit of all four sections of Indus Home Appliances (Fans, Kitchen & Gas appliances, Washing machine & Air coolers, and Plastic appliances) observed their complete manufacturing from raw material to finished product.
- Developed marketing campaign for Indus 30 watt fan from scratch
- Visited Faisalabad main markets to conduct market survey of Indus fans
- Visited Faisalabad to reach potential distributes and dealers of Indus fans
- Visited Gujar Khan main markets to reach potential distributes and dealers of Indus fans

- Participated in telemarketing campaign of 30watt fan to find potential customers
- Promotion of 30watt fan through YouTube channels by inviting unboxing fans youtubers
- Meeting with Chinese delegations

Primary Teacher | Little Toes & Montessori | Gujranwala | 10/2023 – 11-2023

- Teaching students of primary classes
- Giving them the confidence to ask questions
- Giving them new exposure by allowing them to participate in different activities

E-Commerce | Daraz | Online | 04/2023 – 11/2023

- Selling Make up and beauty products on Daraz
- Selling disposable items on Daraz

Graphic Design | Fiver | Freelance | 2022

- Designing logo for small business
- Designing online digital advertisements and post for small businesses

Clotonline.pk | Sales Person | Lahore | 2021

- Dealing with Customers
- Reaching out to the potential customers
- Delivering the products to customers
- Retaining loyal customers

Social Work

Volunteer | KareKamal | Gujranwala | 2020 – 2023

- Old Home Visits
- Orphanage visits
- Cloth drives
- Food drives
- Blanked Drives

Education

• BBA(Hons.) | Marketing | Punjab University | Pakistan | 07/2024

Certifications

- Graphic Design | DigiSkills | Graphic Design | NS Graphics
- SEO | NS Graphics